englishdaily626.com 2004-12-12

# Privacy Policy

_**Information Collection**_

**Registration**  
Registration is not required to use this site, with the exception of the Chat Room section, where users must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information including a username, password, and valid email address. We do not use this information for other purposes other than informing users about new content.

**Information Use**  
All information collected by English Daily is of a non-personal nature. English Daily records aggregate information such as number of users, location, server type, and method of arriving at English Daily. This information is not sold or given to third parties under any circumstances. 

**Cookies**  
We do not use cookies on the users' computer as we believe this will only create unnecessary anxiety on the part of the users who simply want to get some information for their English study. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Website servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**_Communications from the Site_  
 **

**Password given**  
We send all registered members to our Chat Room an email with password to activate their membership for the room. And we advise users to change their password immediately after they have successfully done so.

**Newsletter**  
English Daily does not currently have a newsletter. If we do have a newsletter our policy is as follows:  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Customer Service**  
We do not communicate with users on a regular basis except that they require a service such as a translation that we may, under no obligations, provide to our users.

**_Contents_**

All contents of English Daily are from reliable sources.The contents of English Daily consist of contributions from our users, excerpts from books that are outside the copyright boundary, and material contributed by the English Daily webmaster. Anything that appears here is posted with consent of the author. If any parts of the content are your property, please write in to [honlong@englishdaily626.com](mailto:honlong@englishdaily626.com) for deletion. But we strongly believe in reciprocation though such as placing a link to you as a way to promote each other's sites since it is for the mutual benefit of both parties.

**_Sharing_ **

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Links**  
This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, English Daily, are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the Website, their information is protected both online and off-line.

If users have any questions about the security at our Website, users can send an email to [ honlong@englishdaily626.com](mailto:honlong@englishdaily626.com)

**  
Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use users personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email.
